ILR School Faculty Arbitration Awards /4298
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Faculty Arbitration Awards
1948-1967
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Alexander, Gabriel N.
Campbell, Ralph N.
Dunlop, John T.
Fuller, John J.
Jensen, Vernon H.
McKelvey, Jean T.
Mintz, Frederick M.
Raimon, Robert L.
Waldrin, John E.
/4298
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Awards.
This is a collection of arbitration awards where the arbitrator was a member of the faculty of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. There are seventy awards ranging in date from 1948 to 1967. The majority of the awards are from three arbitrators: Ralph N. Campbell, Vernon H. Jensen, and Jean T. McKelvey.
7577497
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 15, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3001: Jean T. McKelvey Papers /3002: Vernon Jensen Papers /3041: Ralph Campbell Papers /3062: ILR School Public Information Center Publications /4007: Vernon Jensen Additional Records /4128: Vernon Jensen Additional Papers /4137: Vernon Jensen Additional Files /4180: Jean T. McKelvey Additional Papers /4202: Jean T. McKelvey Additional Files 5133: Gabriel Alexander Arbitration Files 5602: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5678: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5789: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5839: Vernon Jenson Additional Arbitration Files 5902: Vernon Jensen Additional Arbitration Files
Alexander, Gabriel N., 1910-; Campbell, Ralph N.(Ralph Norton), 1910-; Dunlop, John T.(John Thomas), 1914-2003; Fuller, John J.; Jensen, Vernon H.; McKelvey, Jean T.(Jean Trepp), 1908-1998; Mintz, Frederick M.; Raimon, Robert L.; Waldrin, John E.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
7577497
- Alexander, Gabriel N., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  One arbitration award
- Campbell, Ralph N., 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Five arbitration awards
- Campbell, Ralph N., 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Four arbitration awards
- Dunlop, John T., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Flagler, John J., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Jensen, Vernon H., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Fifteen arbitration awards
- Jensen, Vernon H., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Sixteen arbitration awards
- Jensen, Vernon H., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Seven arbitration awards
- McKelvey, Jean T., 1953-1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Six arbitration awards
- McKelvey, Jean T., 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Eight arbitration awards
- Mintz, Frederick M., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Raimon, Robert L., 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Two arbitration awards
- Waldrin, John E., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Arbitrator not stated, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)